start
it started from the bottom now we here
started from the bottom now my whole
team here started from the bottom now we
here started from the bottom not a whole
here started fr the Bottom now my whole
team in started from the bottom now we
here started from the I'm not a whole
team here I didn't kept your real from
the jump living at my mama house we ar
you every month I was I was trying to
get it on my own working all night
traffic on the way home and my uncle
calling me like where you at I gave you
the keys till you bring it right back I
just I just think it's funny how it goes
now I'm on a rad half a million for a
show and we started from the bottom now
we here started from the bottom now my
whole team yeah start from the bottom
now we here start it from the bottom not
a whole team here start it from the
bottom now we here start it from the
bottom now the whole team start it the
bottom the whole
team you didn't sign the back of the
check I'm sorry uh you know I wasn't
sure if there was a special teller I
should go to for checks that are this
large ooh 8K uh you know how she got it
dude this right here Drew this
illustration and a sexy ass new dating
website bought it for
$88,000 an alert from your bank
what
no this
illustration it came from her heart
great so do you want this in cash no I
want it in my savings account for
someone who works at the bank I thought
you'd be more responsible with money
ludicrous I also have some business with
the bank I'd like to
cash these nickels and I'll have them in
quarters please thank you so much and
and two
[Music]
and